Angela Robinette

Front End Developer

Email: <u>angela@dev-angela.com</u> Website: <u>https://dev-angela.com/</u> Phone: 406-671-1693

* HTML

* CSS

❖ JavaScript

* Accessibility

Security

Profile:

My coding journey began as a hobby in 2000. First, I worked with HTML and was hooked. A few years later, I learned CSS. Finally, I taught myself a bit of JavaScript for a hidden picture game.

I graduated from Purdue University Global - Summa Cum Laude - with an Associate degree in Software Development/Computer Programming. I love creating beautiful, functional web pages that enhance a user's experience and are secure and accessible to all. During my internship at PGIP-Tech, I was the software development lead. I went back afterward and became a mentor.

Education:

Purdue University Global

4.0 GPA **Associate Degree** in Computer
Programming/Software Development

Graduation – March, 2022

Montana State University Billings, MT

1996-1997 English Major Montana State University Bozeman, MT

1994-1995 General Studies

Experience:

PGIP-Tech Internship

January 2022 – Present

SofDev Mentor

Helping interns with coding questions, most recently React and general OOP problems and questions, accessibility awareness, and front-end security awareness. Dev-angela.com

January 2022 – Present

Owner/Designer/Developer Designed my personal profile website, coded it in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and jQuery, and launched it using FileZilla. **PGIP-Tech Internship** 10/14/2021 – 12/21/2021 **SofDev Manager**

Kept interns on track assigned tasks, worked with Docker, PHP and MySQLi on group project, and helped interns pick a path and the stack they needed.

Skills:

HTML	CSS	Paintshop Pro	JavaScript	Git	Bootstrap
15+ years	15+ years	15+ years	10+ years	2+ years	1+ years
experience	experience	experience	experience	experience	experience

Experience using:

PHP	.Net	Docker	SQL	C#	Angular